I'm a Lama Duma Lama you assume I'm a human what I gotta do to get it through to you
I'm super human innovative and I made a robber so that anything you say can speak a shagging off of me
And it'll be you and devastating more than ever demonstrating how to give them all the fucking audicates
I feel like it's never fading never fading and I know the haters are forever waiting for the day to think
Cause yeah I fell off to be celebrating cause I know the way to get them motivated I make elevating music
You make elevator music oh he's too mainstream well that's what they do when they can tell us to confuse it
It's not hip hop it's pop cause I found a colorway to fuse it with rock, shockwrap, whipdop
Throw and lose yourself I make them lose it
I don't know how to make songs like that I don't know what words to use
Let me know when it occurs to you while I'm ripping anyone of these verses
It's you it's curtains I'm inadvertently hurting you